Guide to the Microwave Research Institute Technical Reports RG.031
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
Guide to the Microwave Research Institute Technical Reports
1942-1970
RG.031
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
39.0 Linear feet
Sponsor note
This project was made possible in part by a generous grant from the History Programs, American Institute of Physics.
Biographical/Historical note
The Microwave Research Institute was founded at the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (now the Tandon School of Engineering) by Ernst Weber in 1945. It was later renamed the Weber Research Institute in his honor.
Arrangement note
The technical reports are arranged by PIB-MRI number. These numbers are typically chronological, but not always. These reports contain multiple report numbering systems and were often cross-listed with military projects. Please consult the archivist if your citation contains a report number other than PIB-MRI.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research without restrictions.
Scope and Contents note
At this time, PIB-MRI reports from 1942-1963 are listed. Please check back frequently, as new reports are added.
Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Microwave Research Institute.; Weber, Ernst; Physics
- Series I: Report numbers PIBMRI 0-100, 1942-1945
  - Junction Effect of Two Unequal Matched Coaxial Lines, PIBMRI-2-42, 1942 September; Weber, Ernst (Volume PIBMRI-2-42)
    Technical report number(s)
    PIBMRI-2-42
    PIB 1
    ATI 24 888
  - Theory of Coaxial Attenuators, PIBMRI-8-42, 1942 September 21; Griemsmann, John W. E.; Weber, Ernst (Volume PIBMRI-8-42)
    PIBMRI-8-42
    PIB 3
    ATI 21 765
  - Lossless Coaxial Exponential Tapers, PIBMRI-15-43, 1943 May 20; Peskin, Edward; Weber, Ernst (Volume PIBMRI-15-43)
    PIBMRI-15-43
    PIB 5
    ATI 24 995
  - Notes on the Use of Bolometers for Ultra-High Frequency Attenuation Measurements, PIBMRI-22-43, 1943 June 2; Ebert, John (Volume PIBMRI-22-43)
    PIBMRI-22-43
    PIB 7
    ATU 15 177
  - The 1B2 Bolometer Terminal, PIBMRI-23-43, 1943 June 11; Ebert, John; Johnson, Stanley; Weber, Ernst (Volume PIBMRI-23-43)
    PIBMRI-23-43
    PIB 8
    ATI 15 175
    Armed Services Technical Information Agency (U.S.).
  - P.I.B. Metallized-Glass Attenuators and Miscellaneous R.F. Test Accessories, PIBMRI-43-44, 1945 April; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-43-44)
    PIBMRI-43-44
    R-43-44
    P.I.B. 23
    Division 14 Report No. 360 (sponsored by NDRC of OSRD)
    Contract No. OEMsr-335
  - Scattering and Propagation of Electromagnetic Waves in Bounded Parametrically Modulated Media, PIBMRI-67-1374, 1968 June; Peng, S. (Volume PIBMRI-67-1374)
    PIBMRI-67-1347
    AD 677 333
    Contract No. AF 49(638)-1402 (for Air Force Office of Scientific Research Office of Aerospace Research)
    Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Department of Electrophysics.
  - Research Forecasts in Electronics for the Office of Naval Research, PIBMRI-69-006, 1969 July; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. (Volume PIBMRI-69-006)
    PIBMRI-69-006
    AD 700 109
  - Frequency Sensitivity of Metallized-Glass Attenuator Inserts Type TMS-4PB, PIBMRI-79-45, 1945 May 11; Nelson, Harry C. (Volume PIBMRI-79-45)
    PIBMRI-79-45
    R-79-45
    PIB-47
    Division 14, NDRC, Report No. 477
  - Conference on Metallized-Glass Plate Program at P.I.B. Research, PIBMRI-84-45, 1945 May 22; Weber, Ernst (Volume PIBMRI-84-45)
    PIBMRI-84-45
    R-84-45
    PIB 57
    ATI 61 059
    Division 14, NDRC Report No. 479
    Contract OEWsr-355
  - Accuracy of Attenuation Measurements Made with the Ballantine Voltmeter, PIBMRI-85-45, 1945 May 30; Nelson, Harry C. (Volume PIBMRI-85-45)
    PIBMRI-85-45
    R-85-45
    PIB 52
    ATI 62 066
    Division 14, NDRC Report No. 480
  - Microwave Resistance Comparator, PIBMRI-86-45, 1945 May 22; Ebert, John (Volume PIBMRI-86-45)
    PIBMRI-86-45
    PIB 53
    ATI 15 160
  - Frequency Sensitivity of Metallized-Glass Attenuator Inserts Type TMS-3PB, PIBMRI-87-45, 1945 May 20; Nelson, Harry C. (Volume PIBMRI-87-45)
    PIBMRI-87-45
    PIB 54
    ATI 15 129
  - The TMX-16 PB Metallized-Glass Plate for X-Band Fixed Attenuator, 25 db, PIBMRI-89-45, 1945 June 2; Giordano, Anthony B.
    PIB 56
    ATI 62 017
    Division 14, NDRC Report No. 484
  - The TMX-24 PB Metallized-Glass Plate for X-Band Fixed Attenuator Pads of 10 db and 13 db, PIBMRI-91-45, 1945 June 26; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-91-45)
    PIBMRI-91-45
    ATI 62 013
    Division 14, NDRC Report No. 485
  - A Resistive Variable Attenuator for K-band with 40 db Maximum Attenuation, PIBMRI-92-45, 1945 May 31; Ebert, John; Johnson, S. (Volume PIBMRI-92-45)
    PIBMRI-92-45
    PIB 58
    ATI 61 458
    Division 14, NDRC Report No. 486
  - Electrical Performance of Metallized-Glass Attenuators for TS-147/UP in Extended-X-band PIBMRI-93-45, 1945 July 6; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-93-45)
    PIBMRI-93-45
    PIB 59
    ATI 62 016
    Division 14, NDRC Report No. 487
- Series II: Report numbers PIBMRI 101-200, 1945-1949
  - Precision Metallization of Glass, PIBMRI-103-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-103-45)
    PIBMRI-103-45
    R-103-45
    NDRC Division 14, Report No. 521
  - Fixed Value Metallized-Glass Coaxial Attenuators, PIBMRI-104-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-104-45)
    PIBMRI-104-45
    R-104-45
    NDRC Division 14, Report No. 522
  - Variable Metallized-Glass Coaxial Attenuators, PIBMRI-105-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-105-45)
    PIBRMI-105-45
    R-105-45
    NDRC Division 14, report No. 523
  - Metallized-Glass Bolometers, PIBMRI-106-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-106-45)
    PIBMRI-106-45
    R-106-45
    NDRC-524
  - The Development of Metallized-Glass Attenuating Elements for X--Band Wave Guide, PIBRMI-107-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBRMI-107-45)
    PIBRMI-107-45
    R-107-45
    NDRC Report No. 525
  - Metallized-Glass Wave Guide Attenuators, PIBMRI-108-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-108-45)
    PIBMRI-108-45
    R-108-45
    NDRC 526
  - The Development of Metallized-Glass Attenuators for Test Set TS-147/UP, PIBMRI-109-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-109-45)
    PIBMRI-109-45
    R-109-45
    NDRC, Report No. 527
  - R-F Components for Microwave Bridges, PIBMRI-110-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-110-45)
    PIBMRI-110-45
    R-110-45
    NDRC 528
  - Microwave Power Measurement with Bolometers, PIBMRI-111-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-111-45)
    PIBMRI-111-45
    R-111-45
    NDRC 529
  - Type "N" Connector Design and Tests, PIBMRI-112-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-112-45)
    PIBMRI-112-45
    R-112-45
    NDRC 530
  - Microwave Attenuation Standards, PIBMRI-113-45, Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-113-45)
    PIBMRI-113-45
    R-113-45
    NDRC 531
    Contained within the report: PIB A-195-A, PIB-354-A, PIB-A-347A
  - Microwave Attenuation Measurement, PIBMRI-114-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-114-45)
    PIBMRI-114-45
    R-114-45
    NDRC 532
  - Development of Miscellaneous R-F Line Components, PIBMRI-115-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-115-45)
    PIBMRI-115-45
    R-115-45
    NDRC 533
  - Precision Metallized-Glass Resistor Units, PIBMRI-116-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-116-45)
    PIBMRI-116-45
    R-116-45
    NRDC-534
  - Final Report for OSRD Contract OEMsr-335 Sponsored by NDRC, Division 14, Project No. 15.02, PIBMRI-117-45, 1945 October 31; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Graduate Electrical Engineering Department.. (Volume PIBMRI-117-45)
    PIBMRI-117-45
    R-117-45
    NDRC-535
  - Basic Aspects in the Design of Cut-Off Attenuators, PIBMRI-120-46, 1946 Februrary 11; Laemmel, Arthur (Volume PIBMRI-120-46)
    PIBMRI-120-46
    PIB 71
  - Quarterly Report on Research and Development of Attenuators Over the Frequency Range of 8,200 mc/sec. to 39,000 mc/sec. for the Period of June - August 1950, PIBMRI-125.29-50, 1950 September 20; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-125.29-50)
    PIBMRI-125.29-50
    R-125.29-50
    PIB 76.29
    ATI 155 329
  - VSWR Measurements on Type "N" Cable Connectors from 2.5 to 10.0 Kilomegacycles per Second, PIBMRI-136-46, 1946 November; Griemsmann, John W. E.; Nadler, Leo (Volume PIBMRI-136-46)
    PIBMRI-136-46
    R-136-46
    PIB 87
    ATI 24 711
  - Response of Thermionic Vacuum Tubes Under Uniform Emission to Applied Signal Voltages, PIBMRI-135-47, 1947 February 18; Gamble, Edward H. (Volume PIBMRI-135-47)
    PIBMRI-135-47
    PIB 86
    ATI 173 848
  - Source Distribution Functions for Small High Gain Antennas, PIBMRI-137-47, 1947 April 4; Laemmel, Arthur (Volume PIBMRI-137-47)
    PIBMRI-137-47
    PIB 88
  - Method for Improving Resolution in a Two Dimensional Scanning Process, PIBMRI-138-47, 1947 April 7; Laemmel, Arthur (Volume PIBMRI-138-47)
    PIBMRI-138-47
    PIB 89
  - Synthesis of Lossy Microwave Structures for Broad Band Matching with Applications to the Design of Coaxial Attenuators, PIBMRI-139-47, 1947 March 31; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-139-47)
    PIBMRI-139-47
    PIB 90
  - Impedance Description of Planar Gratings, PIBMRI-140-47, 1947 April; Marcuvitz, Nathan (Volume PIBMRI-140-47)
    PIBMRI-140-47
    PIB 91
    ATI 43 279
  - The Design of Wide-Band Coaxial, Fixed Pad Attenuators for the Frequency Band 4,000 to 10,000 No/sec., PIBMRI-141-47, 1947 April 3; Carlin, Herbert J.; Fox, Arnold, M. (Volume PIBMRI-141-47)
    PIBMRI-141-47
    R-141-47
    PIB 92
    PIB 116
  - Theoretical Study of Metal Film Water Calorimeter for Microwave Power Measurements, PIBMRI-142-47, 1947 April; Kahal, Robert (Volume PIBMRI-142-47)
    PIBMRI-142-47
    R-142-47
    PIB 93
  - Influence of Current Flow and Magnetic Fields During the Formation of Thin Metallic Films by Evaporation, PIBMRI-143-47, 1947 April 18; Schleuning, Hubert W. (Volume PIBMRI-143-47)
    PIBMRI-143-47
    R-143-47
  - A Note on MRI Performance, PIBMRI-147-47, 1947 May 7; DiToro, Michael J. (Volume PIBMRI-147-47)
    PIBMRI-147-47
    R-147-47
    PIB 95
  - Analytical and Experimental Study of Magnetic Amplifiers, PIBMRI-149-47, 1947 June 10; Stateman, Murray (Volume PIBMRI-149-47)
    PIBMRI-149-47
    PIB 98
    ATI 205 922
  - Bibliography Report on Phase (A) of Contract No. N60R1-98, Task Order IV, PIBMRI-150-47, 1947 June 23; Gold, Bernard (Volume PIBMRI-150-47)
    PIBMRI-150-47
    PIB 99
    ATI 37 589
  - On the Representation and Measurement of Wavelength Discontinuities, PIBMRI-151-47, 1947 June; Marcuvitz, Nathan (Volume PIBMRI-151-47)
    PIBMRI-151-47
    PIB 100 ATI 31 748
  - Bibliography Report on Phase (C) of Contract No. N60RI-98 Task Order IV, PIBMRI-153-47, 1947 June 23; Stateman, Murray (Volume PIBMRI-153-47)
    PIBMRI-153-47
    R-153-47
    PIB 102
  - Transients in Frequency Modulation, I. Frequency Pulse Applied to Ideal Band Pass Filter, PIBMRI-154-47, 1947 July; Gold, Bernard (Volume PIBMRI-154-47)
    PIBMRI-154-47
    R-154-47
    PIB 103
    ATI 57 944
  - Transients in Frequency Modulation, II. The Response of a Discriminator Type Network to a Frequency Step, PIBMRI-154.1-47, 1947 September 26; Gold, Bernard (Volume PIBMRI-154.1-47)
    PIBMRI-154.1-47
    R-154.1-47
    PIB 103.1
  - Transients in Frequency Modulation, III. The Solution of Steady State Problems in Frequency Modulation, PIBMRI-154.2-48, 1948 October 21; Gold, Bernard (Volume PIBMRI-154.2-48)
    PIBMRI-154.2-48
    R-154.2-48
    PIB 103.2
  - Transients in Frequency Modulation System with Monotonic Phase Distortion, PIBMRI-155-47, 1947; Edelberg, Seymour (Volume PIBMRI-155-47)
    PIBMRI-155-47
    R-155-47
    PIB 104
    ATI 31 680
  - A Harmonic Generator for the 10,000 MC/SEC to 12650 MC/SEC Frequency Range, PIBRMI-156-47, 1947 July; Nelson, Harry C. (Volume PIBRMI-156-47)
    PIBRMI-156-47
    R-156-47
    PIB 105
    ATI 27 088
  - Waveguide Circuit Theory: Coupling of Waveguides by Small Apertures, PIBMRI-157-47, 1947 July; Marcuvitz, Nathan (Volume PIBMRI-157-47)
    PIBMRI-157-47
    R-157-47
    PIB 106
  - A Calibrated Heterodyne Receiver for Micro-Wave Attenuation Measurements, PIBMRI-161-47, 1947 September; Nelson, Harry C. (Volume PIBMRI-161-47)
    PIBMRI-161-47
    R-161-47
    PIB 108
    ATI 31 293
  - Operation of the Summation of Type Wattmeter Bridge, PIBRMI-164-47, 1947 November 6; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBRMI-164-47)
    PIBRMI-164-47
    R-164-47
    PIB 110
    ATI 155 461
  - A Direct Reading D-C Bridge for Microwave Bolometer Power Measurements, PIBMRI-165-47, 1947 December 29; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-165-47)
    PIBMRI-165-47
    R-165-47
    PIB 111
    AD 40335a
  - Attenuation Characteristics of a Tapered Dielectric Coaxial Attenuator, PIBMRI-167-48, 1948 October 15; Blass, Judd; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-167-48)
    PIBMRI-167-48
    R-167-48
    PIB 114
  - Preliminary Bibliography on Impedance Measurements, PIBMRI-168-48, 1948 April 7; Oliner, Arthur A. (Volume PIBMRI-168-48)
    PIBMRI-168-48
    R-168-48
    PIB 115
  - V.S.W.R. Data on B.N.C. Connectors for the Frequency Range 2.4 to 10 KMC/SEC (An Types UG88/U, UG89/U, And UG306/U), PIBMRI-169-48, 1948 May 4; Griemsmann, John W. E.; Nadler, Leo (Volume PIBMRI-169-48)
    PIBMRI-169-48
    R-169-48
  - Interim Report on Electromagnetic Theory Applied to Radiation Problems for the Period from 1 May 48 to 31 May 48 Radiation from Slots, PIBMRI-171.1-48, 1948 June; Marcuvitz, Nathan (Volume PIBMRI-171.1-48)
    PIBMRI-171.1-48
    R-171.1-48
  - Report on 1. Evaluation of Bolometer Errors in The Measurement of Attenuation Using a Bolometer Detector 2. Construction of a Bolometer Element for Waveguide 1/2" x 1/4" x .040", PIBMRI-172-48, 1948 June; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-172-48)
    Other Finding Aids note
    PIBMRI-172-48
    R-172-48
    PIB 118
  - A Survey of Phase Changers Used in the Microwave Region, PIBMRI-175-48, 1948 August 30; Altschuler, Helmut M. (Volume PIBMRI-175-48)
    PIBMRI-175-48
    R-175-48
    PIB 120
  - Report on 1. Vibration Test of 2 x 1.064 Guide Size Glass Attenuator Plates 2. Preliminary Test of the Above Plate Mounted in a Casing, PIBMRI-176-48, 1948 August 4; Schleuning, Hubert W. (Volume PIBMRI-176-48)
    PIBMRI-176-48
    R-176-48
    PIB 121
  - Analytical Study of an Unbiased Bridge Type Magnetic Amplifier, PIBMRI-177-48, 1948 November 19; Stateman, Murray; Weber, Ernst (Volume PIBMRI-177-48)
    PIBMRI-177-48
    R-177-48
    PIB 122
  - The Natural Frequency of Vibration of a Glass Plate Attenuator, PIBMRI-179-48, 1948 August 24; Schleuning, Hubert W. (Volume PIBMRI-179-48)
    PIBMRI-179-48
    R-179-48
    PIB 124
  - Analysis of Small A-C Signal Response of a Space-Charge-Limited Parallel-Plane Diode Having an Oxide Cathode, PIBMRI-180-48, 1948 September 10; Dalman, G. Conrad (Volume PIBMRI-180-48)
    PIBMRI-180-48
    R-180-48
    PIB 125
  - The Construction and Operation of Broadband Bolometer Powermeters for 20 to 10,000 MC/SEC and 25 μw - 5w, PIBMRI-181-48, 1948 September 8; Carlin, Herbert J.; Torgow, Eugene (Volume PIBMRI-181-48)
    PIBMRI-181-48
    R-181-48
    PIB 126
  - Steady State Response of Physical Networks to a F.M. Wave, PIBMRI-182-48, 1948 October 26; Brogan, J. (Volume PIBMRI-182-48)
    PIBMRI-182-48
    R-182-48
    PIB 127
  - The Impedance of a Narrow Lossy, Inductive Obstacle in a Rectangular Waveguide, PIBMRI-184-48, 1948 December 16; Edelberg, Seymour (Volume PIBMRI-184-48)
    PIBMRI-184-48
    R-184-48
    PIB 129
  - A Study of Directional Couplers with Emphasis on Frequency Characteristics, PIBMRI-187-49, 1949 January 20; Tanenbaum, Morton S. (Volume PIBMRI-187-49)
    PIBMRI-187-49
    R-187-49
    PIB 131
  - VSWR Data on H.N. Connectors for the Frequency Range 1.0 to 10.0 KMC./SEC. (AN Types UG 59A/U, UG 60A/U, UG 21/U, UG 333/U, UG 334/U and UG 495/U, PIBMRI-189-49, 1949 April 22; Griemsmann, John W. E.; Nadler, Leo (Volume PIBMRI-189-49)
    PIBMRI-189-49
    R-189-49
    PIB 133
  - Quarterly Report on Microwave Interference Investigations for the Frequency Range 1,000-40,000 MC/SEC for the Period of November 1, 1948 to January 31, 1949, PIBMRI-192.1-49, 1949 February 21; Griemsmann, John W. E. (Volume PIBMRI-192.1-49)
    PIBMRI-192.1-49
    R-192.1-49
    PIB 136
    AD 53 072
  - The Representation, Measurement, and Calculation of Equivalent Circuits for Waveguide Discontinuities with Application to Rectangular Slots, PIBMRI-193-49, 1949; Marcuvitz, Nathan (Volume PIBMRI-193-49)
    PIBMRI-193-49
    R-193-49
    PIB 137
  - Final report of Improved Impedance Measuring Methods Over the Frequency Range of 100 to 10,000 mc/sec, PIBMRI-195-49, 1951 June 5; Altschuler, Helmut M.; Laemmel, Arthur (Volume PIBMRI-195-49)
    PIBMRI-195-49
    R-195-49
    PIB 139
  - Measurement of Waveguide Impedances with a Circular Side Arm, PIBMRI-195-49, 1949 March 14; Laemmel, Arthur (Volume PIBMRI-195-49)
  - Steady State Analysis of a Magnetic Amplifier, PIBMRI-196-49, 1949 April 13; Esselman, Walter; Smith, Edward J. (Volume PIBMRI-196-49)
    PIBMRI-196-49
    R-196-49
    PIB 140
  - A Short 3/8" Line-to-7/8" Line Precision Broadband Adapter, PIBMRI-197-49, 1949 March 21; Albanese, Victor; Griemsmann, John W. E. (Volume PIBMRI-197-49)
    PIBMRI-148-49
    R-197-49
    PIB 141
  - Tests of High Power Coaxial Loads for Microwave Powermeters, PIBMRI-198-49, 1949 April 26; Tanenbaum, Morton S. (Volume PIBMRI-198-49)
    PIBMRI-198-49
    R-198-49
    PIB 149
  - A Broadband High Power Microwave Attenuator, PIBMRI-199-49, 1949 April 25; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-199-49)
    PIBMRI-199-49
    R-199-49
    PIB 143
    AD 40 335-C
  - Bolometer Measurement of Microwave Power Over Broad Frequency Bands, PIBMRI-200-49, 1949 April 25; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-200-49)
    PIBMRI-200-49
    R-200-49
    PIB 144
- Series III: Report number PIBMRI 201-300, 1949-1950
  - The Construction and Operation of Broadband Bolometer Meters for 1,000-10,000 MC/SEC and 5 Watts-1,000 Watts, PIBMRI-201-49, 1949 April 26; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-201-49)
    PIBMRI-201-49
    R-201-49
    PIB 145
  - Tests Performed by the Microwave Research Institute on Powermeter ME - 19 (XW-1)/U to Satisfy Requirements of Contract W33-038-ac-13848, PIBMRI-202-49, 1949 April 25; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-202-49)
    PIBMRI-202-49
    R-202-49
    PIB 146
  - Tests Performed by the Microwave Research Institute on Powermeter ME - 20 (XW-1)/U to Satisfy Requirements of Contract W33-038-ac-13848, PIBMRI-203-49, 1949 April 25; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-203-49)
    PIBMRI-203-49
    R-203-49
    PIB 147
  - Tests Performed by the Microwave Research Institute on Powermeter ME - 20 (XW-1)/U to Satisfy Requirements of Contract W33-038-ac-13848, PIBMRI-204-49, 1949 April 25; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-204-49)
    PIBMRI-204-49
    R-204-49
    PIB 148
  - Final Report on the Development of Powermeters Over the Frequency Range 20 Mc/sec to 10,000 Mc/sec and 25 μw to 1,000 Watts, PIBMRI-205-49, 1949 April 26; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-205-49)
    PIBMRI-205-49
    R-205-49
  - Development of Metallized-Glass Attenuators for Waveguide Size 2" x 1" x 0.064", PIBMRI-206-49, 1949 May 6; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-206-49)
    PIBMRI-206-49
    R-206-49
    PIB 150
  - Magnetic Amplifier Core Properties Phase (C), PIBMRI-207-49, 1949 May 13; Benjamin, Fred (Volume PIBMRI-207-49)
    PIBMRI-207-49
    R-207-49
    PIB 151
  - Report on Phase I of the Study of Data Transmission, General Theory of Communication, PIBMRI-208-49, 1949 July 13; Laemmel, Arthur (Volume PIBMRI-208-49)
    PIBMRI-208-49
    R-208-49
    PIB 152
  - Oxide Cathode Resistance and Rectifying Characteristics, PIBMRI-209-49, 1950 January 12; Dalman, G. Conrad (Volume PIBMRI-209-49)
    PIBMRI-209-49
    R-209-49
    PIB 153
  - Final Report on the Development of Broadband Microwave Attenuators for Navy Contract NObs-28376 Issued in 2 Sections, Section I - Coaxial Line Attenuators, PIBMRI-217-49, 1949 May 26; Carlin, Herbert J. (Volume PIBMRI-217-49)
    PIBMRI-217-49
    R-217-49
    PIB 161
  - Final Report on the Development of Broadband Microwave Attenuators for Navy Contract NObs-28376 Issued in 2 Sections, Section II - Rectangular Waveguide Attenuators, PIBMRI-218-49, 1949 May 25; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-218-49)
    PIBMRI-218-49
    R-218-49
    PIB 162
  - Final Report NObs 28372 (Issued in Two Volumes) Volume I: Radio Frequency Cable Connector Measurements and Developments, PIBMRI-219-49, 1949 June 10; Griemsmann, John W. E. (Volume PIBMRI-219-49)
    PIBMRI-219-49
    R-219-49
    PIB 163
  - Quarterly Progress Report for the Period May 1, 1950 to July 31, 1950 on Dielectric Breakdown Investigations, PIBMRI-220.14-50, 1950 November 6; Griemsmann, John W. E. (Volume PIBMRI-220.14-50)
    PIB-164.14
    R-220.14-50
    Contract No. W36-039-sc-44491
    Signal Corps Project No. 32-2005-34
    Dept. of the Army Project No. 3-93-00-500
  - Quarterly Progress Report for the Period August 1, 1950 to October 31, 1950 on Dielectric Breakdown Investigations, PIBMRI-220.17-51, 1951 January 24; Griemsmann, John W. E.; Sucher, Max (Volume PIBMRI-220.17-51)
    PIB 164.17
    R-220.17-51
    ATI 94312
  - Step by Step Method for Investigation of Magnetic Amplifiers, PIBMRI-221-49, 1949 July 15; Cacho, Luis Gimenez (Volume PIBMRI-221-49)
    PIB 166
    R-221-49
  - Bimonthly Progress Report on Attenuators December 1952 - January 1953 on Navy Contract NObsr-43360 "Attenuators," PIBMRI-222.22-53, 1953 February 9; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-222.22-53)
    PIB 167.22
    R-222.22-53
    ATI 32-560
  - Straight Line Analysis of Full-Wave Magnetic Amplifier, PIBMRI-223-49, 1949 September 8; Esselman, Walter (Volume PIBMRI-223-49)
    PIB-168
    R-223-49
    Contract N6ori-98
  - Bimonthly Progress Report for the Months of June 1953 - July 1953 on Navy Contract N0bsr-43360 "Attenuators," PIBMRI-222.25-53, 1953 July 16; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-222.25-53)
    PIB-167.25
    R-222.25-53
    AD 32 559
    Contract No. N0bsr-43360
    Index No. 100-402
  - Bimonthly Progress Report on Attenuators August 1953 - September 1953 on Navy Contract N0bsr-43360 "Attenuators," PIBMRI-222.26-53, 1953 October 7; Giordano, Anthony B. (Volume PIBMRI-222.26-53)
    PIB-167.26
    R-222.26-53
    AD 32 558
  - A study of the Characteristics of Vacuum Tubes with Oxide Cathodes at Low and High Frequencies, PIBMRI-224-49, 1949 October 12; Dalman, G. Conrad (Volume PIBMRI-224-49)
    PIB-169
    R-224-49
  - A Resistance Directional Coupler for Waveguide, PIBMRI-225-49, 1949 September 27; Tanenbaum, Morton S. (Volume PIBMRI-225-49)
    PIB-170
    R-225-49
    Contract No. W33-038-sc-18115